A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Hurry. You must hurry, Stein. It's time to shed your fake skin.
Give in and do what must be done.
Look for the light. The way out is up ahead.
Stop right there, Stein.
Where do you think you're going? We should be locked in the laboratory.
That's what I'm doing, trying to find my way back.
The fog is too thick, and I think I've lost my way.
You have. The madness is taking over.
I don't understand. What are you talking about?
Haven't you realized it yet, Stein? I am the law's hound.
I guard this door so no one with a taint of madness can pass through.
You had better not come any closer.
What's happening?
I'm falling down to my shadow
息をひそめて
待っている that dream life
Don't scare me
君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢だとしても
テレブル君のために
星を裂き
飾り付けた
Black paper
知りてくれたなら
When you're lost, you're young
Forever with your soul
見上げば輝く
Dina, you're worth me
I wonder where everyone is
They canceled morning classes
since no one showed up
That bunch of cowards
They're probably too afraid of the madness to come outside
I bet they're all at home right now
hiding under their beds like babies
But there's no need to be scared
Not with me here
I'll tear that Kishin apart in a second
It'll take a whole second
You're losing your edge
Hi, Sol
Yo
You'll tear your pants
Once you see the Kishin
Oh, shut up
Maka's not with you?
Nope, she isn't
She won't be coming later either
She says she can't concentrate
She's too worried about Krona and the nutty professor
Hang in a little longer
They let Medusa go, didn't they?
After that
What excuse can they have for keeping you locked up?
Yeah
But what's going on with Professor Stein?
Has he come back yet?
Please tell me
Don't you think Professor Stein's disappearance has something to do with Lady Medusa?
It's possible
But you don't need to be worried about that
It's Professor Stein
He's tougher than he looks
He'll come back to us
Call off the search?
But why?
He's already left the city
The way things are right now
We can't afford to send anyone else to look
But it's so obvious what he's doing
He's gone after Medusa
If so, it's even worse than we thought
No one from the Academy
Can so much as lay a finger on that witch
Anyway, I came to tell you
We have a Death Scythe mission for you
Time to get it together
Get back to work
Is that all you care about?
You're not just a Death Scythe
You're his partner too
How can you give up so easily?
He's been fighting all this time
Keeping the madness locked in
Maybe he's stronger than you think he is, Marie
Impressive, Medusa
No witch has ever been able to strike a bargain with the Grim Reaper before
It's so simple now
All we do is sit and watch
Arachne and the Reaper will destroy each other
And we won't have to lift a finger
Of course, if the plan doesn't work
Both of them will come looking for us
And that could get ugly real quick
The Reaper won't break the contract
He's too honorable
And Arachne?
Well, the Kishin will destroy her
If the Reaper doesn't get to her first
We just wait a little longer to make our move
Where are you off to this time?
I've got a little appointment with my lover
Twirl round and round
A new world in which the Doc dances?
Don't cry
If you can make it through this anguish
Happiness will be waiting on the other side
No matter how lost you feel
There's always a way out
Are you little girls lost in here too?
What do you mean girls?
It's just me
I'm all alone with you
Just you and me and that's okay
I came here to get you
Come with me
We'll follow the path
Pretty soon it'll lead us right out of here
Can't you see she's a witch?
You can't stay here forever, you know
You have somebody waiting for you
It's time for you to leave this place
But be careful of the witch
If you let the madness take you
You'll never find the way out
But how do I leave?
That's easy
All you have to do is think about where you're supposed to be
Where I'm supposed to be?
Who are you, kid?
Zero reaction to magic
It's as still as a stone
I could use my wavelength to activate it
No, there's gotta be some trick to it
How am I supposed to think straight
When all I have to drink is this awful coffee
Now look what I've done
The coffee's spilling everywhere
What's that?
Way to go
This is a breakthrough
Crafty Abon
Hiding a secret page right in the front cover
It's the information we're looking for
To activate Brew, we have to find the key
It's another magic tool
We should send someone out immediately
Kid could handle the mission easily
Hmm
We're not exactly on the best terms right now
I don't know if he'll take it on
He's still suspicious about what we're planning with the tools
Too much is going on for him to be acting like a petulant child
You're his father, tell him he doesn't have a choice
There's one more thing
We need someone else
I'd like you to call on Uncle Bob for assistance
Um, yeah
Who's he again?
How could you forget?
He's the owner of the coffee shop nearby
The only coffee so delicious it'll make you want to dance
Come on everybody sing with me
I'm falling apart at the seams without my mandaling coffee beans
Oh
Mandolin?
Mandaling man
I can't concentrate without Uncle Bob's rumba coffee
I should have found that secret page long before now
If I keep going like this, my work will continue to suffer
Now now, is it really that bad?
Yes
Normally, I'd never pause to ask for outside help
Pause?
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow
It smells so good I'm almost drooling
Keep your pants on, lunch will be ready in just a few more minutes
We're calling this plate of chard fish lunch?
Besides, isn't it Maka's turn to cook today anyway?
Where is she?
She locked herself in her room and she refuses to come out
She should really eat some lunch though
I'm sure a bite of my yummy fish would cheer her up
So, give me a hand
How about you be my taste tester?
Huh?
Here, open up and say aww
Ah
Hey, what the hell?
Huh?
How could they let her go like that?
After everything she's done to Professor Stein and Krona?
I have to stop
If I keep thinking about it, I'm gonna go mad too
Mail for you
A postcard from Mama
The place where I'm supposed to be, huh?
Come back here, Stein!
The laboratory...
It's a good thing I'm home now, but I still violated my curfew and ran off without telling anyone
I wonder what excuse I should use
Marie!
What are you doing, Marie?
From up here?
The city looks so small
Kind of like a prison floating in the clouds
Don't you think?
Somewhere out there
I'm sure there's a world that will fit you better
Goodbye, Stein
Marie!
Aw, looks like she died
But wait, isn't that what you wanted?
You never cared about her the way she cared about you
Bye, Marie
You went through the wrong exit
The madness has taken over just like I thought it would
What happened to Marie
What happened to Marie?
No need to worry
You'll forget everything once I'm done with you
Everyone you knew in your old life
Even your own name
What are you going to do to me?
You have to be punished
You broke the law and gave in to madness
I need to cut you open and fix you up
Stop it!No don't!
So many pretty pictures
Mama sent one to me every time she went somewhere new
She hasn't sent one in a long time
I've been kinda worried about her
Your mom must be a pretty amazing lady
A minute ago you were depressed
But now you're all smiley
Yeah
So what place did she send you a postcard from this time?
Hey, something's written in the corner
You're right
What is it?
Hey, Maka
Teaching is nothing but trouble
I never thought I'd do it
Look at me now
These kids need someone to help them
I don't think I can quit
But you need me too Stein
Don't you?
Stop it!
The kids can't see you like this
Don't fight it Stein
I'm giving you the chance to be reborn
Let me cut you open
Yes, a new world is waiting
It's time for you to shed your fake skin
Shut up!Shut up!Shut up!
This is the fruit of life
One bite of this and all your suffering will come to an end
You'll feel much better
Don't fall for it
You were reaching for a shadow
An illusion you created
You
I know you
You're me
I know you're nervous but there's no reason to be
Go on, have a sip of your tea
Um...
Oh no, don't tell me you're a coffee drinker too
I don't think I can handle any more tango or rumba or whatever
I want to make a request
Please sir
Please let me leave here and go after Lady Medusa
I want to try and bring back Professor Stein
You're still being held prisoner for your betrayal of the DWMA
And you want me to trust you?
I have to go after them
Maka's always stood up for me, I owe her that much
I have to do this
Okay
You have some things to settle with Medusa as well, don't you?
Yes
My
You've got guts, don't you?
Miss Marie
I ask her to meet us here
She says she wants to talk to you about something
I'm so sorry
This is all my fault, I lied to you
And now Professor Stein's gone
Don't apologize
Lift up your head
I'm not ready to hear apologies from you yet
Maybe someday, but not now
As for Stein
He's too important to be entrusted to you
Not alone
That's why I'm coming
I'm coming
Just then
When I went through that door
I was lost for a moment
I wasn't sure if that's where you meant
The place I'm supposed to be
Weren't you satisfied with your life?
Yes
I was
Even in a world governed by morality
I made it a long time without feeling guilt
But now
But now what?
You finally feel guilt, but you don't understand why
Because instead of fulfilling your own desires
You found something more important
You already know the right choice
You just have to make it
That's why you called me, isn't it?
Open the right door and walk through it
The world you seek is waiting for you
The world that I'm seeking
There's always a way out
The place I'm supposed to be
Oh yeah!
Damn it!
You only made that chance
You can walk through it
The world you seek is waiting for you
The world that I'm seeking
Oh yeah!
Damn it!
You only made that shot because I let you!
Well, you'd better not go so easy on me this time
Because the person who makes this shot
Is the one who beats the Kishi
What?!
Crap!
You idiot!
Come on
With all that's going on
This is what they're doing
I think it's okay
Sometimes you have to take a break
Not you too, Tsubaki
Maka, catch!
Would you quit it?
You know I'm no good at this game, Sol
Here, you go play
Thanks, Maka
Now I'm the one who'll beat the Kishin
How could you betray me like this, Tsubaki?
Aw, you'll be okay
Does it really matter who beats him?
Who cares as long as he's destroyed, right?
Then we can play in peace
Don't space out on us, Maka
Hand over the ball, little girl!
Take this!
Ah!
Hey, it went in
See that? I got the ball in just by using my head
Uh...
So clearly I'm the one who's gonna pound the Kishin into dust
Um, I think something's wrong with your neck
You're playing basketball?
Right now?
Oh, hey kid
You skipped school again, didn't you?
What are you up to anyway?
I came to tell you all something
Do you know where we got our information about the Kishin?
From Medusa
They made a deal with her?
Exactly
They released her because she told them Asherah's location
They took a witch's word just like that
Even if it meant risking students' lives
I don't understand what they're doing
From now on
We have to be careful about who at the academy we trust
Hurry
It's time to shed your fake skin
Stop fighting it
Just keep walking
Don't you see that light?
You're almost there
Is this it?
My exit?
ités
It's time to shed generations
YOU
medusa
Connor
It's an empty pile of stress
This is take place
BIRTH CARIMA
Mama!
What's going on?
It's kind of like, you know.
I agree. It's very, you know.
So what do you know?
Oh, you know. You know.
Oh, I know. But do you?
I definitely know. But I don't know if you know. You know?
I'm lost. What are we talking about?
Um, I don't know.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, charge Baba Yaga's castle.
Things are kind of gloomy.
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.
You know?